Guide to the Stanford University, El Centro Chicano, Records SC0650
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH-2005-210
  - Events and Issues, 1990-1992
    - Chicano Alumni Conference, 4/25/1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Chicano Alumni Conference, 5/4/1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Conference - Racial & Ethnic Relations, Santa Fe, 1990 Jun (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - File - El Centro, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - El Centro Open House, 9/28/91 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - El Centro Chicano Activities, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Continuing Studies Program, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - El Centro Staff Meetings, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Staff Meetings Spring, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - El Centro Staff Meetings, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - CPPC, 1991-1992
    - El Centro Staff Meetings, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - CPPC, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - CPPC-Advisory Group Budget, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - CPPC Registration Card, 1991 Aug (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Diana Conklin (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - CSUF - Visit (Geneva Lopez Iriani), 11/9/1990 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Dean and Outside Projects, 1990-1992
    - Anita de Lucio Mural Presentation, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - CON 900- Computer Class (Cost Policy/Chart of Accounts), 8/6/91 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Dean of Student Office Executive Group, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Dean's Group Meetings (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Children Now - Nonprofit.Org Oakland, 10/6/90 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Emergency Evacuation Planning Environmental Health & Safety, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Cultural Center-Admissions, Centennial, 1991-1992
    - Asian American Activities Center, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - ASSU COP, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - ACOME Report, May 9 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Agenda - Staff Retreat, 1990 Oct 6 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Admissions Issues, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Jim Montoya, Office of Undergraduate Admissions, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Admissions Office-Travel Schedules, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Approaching Stanford, 1990-92 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Alum & Students Reception, 1991 Sep 27 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - CAAG, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Centennial Celebration's Finale Weekend, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - T. Burciaga- Lounge- Display of Posters, 1991 Jul 22 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Community Events, News, Planning Calendar, 1990-1992
    - Calendar & Planning for September Salary Increases, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Centennial Finale Weekend HAAS Center Meetings, 33482 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Centenial Brochure, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Community Calendar, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - CLOC Letter for Parents (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Community Contacts, 33382 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - CGSA J. Fetter Letter, 33196 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - J. Fetter - FM Role Confirmation, 33206 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Tomas Gabriel, 33505 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Dean of Undergraduate Admissions - Search, 33359 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Dixie Cup Article, "Ole Miss Vs. Mississippi State", 33604 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Domestic Partners Policy, 33402 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - DOS Staff Retreat, 33482 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - DOSA Retreat, Los Gatos, 33162 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Matt Duckworth, Communications Class, 33635 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Evergreen Valley College, 33704 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Fire Within COP, 33117 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Financial Aid Advisor Announcement, 33329 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Firetruck House Space, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Graduate Student Issues, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Sergio Guerrero Sequoia Hospital, 33451 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Graduate Student Services Group, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Jose Garcia Frosh Newsstory, 33504 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - HAAS, Letters, Job, 1990-1992
    - First Yr. Trips SU Orientation, Mar-92 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - HAAS Center - Volunteer Coord, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - HAAS Public Service Center, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - HAAS Center - Application (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Hispanic Community Fund, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Iroko Tribute Letters for J. Porras, J. Leckie, Mar-92 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Irvine Folder, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Arturo Islas (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Arturo Islas Memorial Service, 3/13/1991 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Elise Langlois (Contacts for Medical School), Jul-91 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Letter- Admission Outreach Opportunities, 11/8/1990 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - LRSA- Mtg, Sharon Parker, 6/21/1991 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Looking for a Job-Students, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Lulac Education Magazine, Sep-90 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Ted Martinez (Class of '72) - Alum; Info for Sammy Pacheco (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Meyer Library Position & Collections, 5/15/1991 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Midwest Consortium for Latino Research, 8/1/1991 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Guiding Concilio
    - Noticias El Centro Chicano Newsletters (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - El Centro Staff Position Announcements 1995-96 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Coordinators Information 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - El Centro Staff Applications 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Concilio Applications 11/15/94 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Frances and James (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Guiding Concilio Proposals Winter '93-94 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Guiding Concilio Nominations Received 5/95 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Guiding Concilio Nomination Form 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - FM guiding Concilio Proposals 4/94 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Guiding Concilio Application for funding 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - R. Bacchetti 5/13/91 Memo Allocation of funds (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Guiding Concilio 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Guiding Concilio Roster 1/94 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - C. Rise Provost Meeting 1/28/94 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - By Laws Constitution Adopted 4/6/92 Guiding Concilio (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Guiding Concilio Nomination Forms 1990-91 Undergraduate and Graduate (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - La Raza Staff Association Guiding Concilio 5/92 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Guiding Concilio Nominations 1991-92 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Guiding Concilio Student Representative (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Nomination Forms 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Guiding Concilio Nomination forms due May 7 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - By Laws copies (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Guiding Concilio Nominations 5/94 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - El Centro Lounge Reservations 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Guiding Concilio Appreciation Certificates 1991-92 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Staff Nominations Guiding Concilio 1992 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - LRSA Nominations Received 93-94 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Guiding C. Staff Nominations 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - R. Bacchetti Letter 7/22/92 Follow up on 1992 Awards (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - RB2 049 provost guiding Concilio Account Expenditure Statement 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Announcement of Provost Funds 10/92 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Guiding Concilio Roster 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Letter to President Casper 11/10/92 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - VPSR Questionnaire (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Provost Funds 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Guiding Concilio Grant Proposals winter 1993 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Guiding Concilio 1992-93 (FM) (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Provost Funds Carryover 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Guiding Concilio community Meeting FM 12-3-92 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Leeberman Provost Fund 4-4-93 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Guiding Concilio Proposals Spring 1993 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Guiding Concilio Grant Proposals SNAP checks 92-93 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Survey El Centro Chicano Use 3/93 Guiding Concilio (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Study of El Centro Chicano Use (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Random Pies (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - FM Photos 1990 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - El Dia de los Muertos 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - University events and services info sheet 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Audiovisual services and facility scheduling 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Program facilities 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - El Centro Chicano Staff Time Schedules Spring 1991 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Ambassador Program (Annie Roskin) (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Annual Review Panel 5/90 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - El Centro Open House 1990-91 10-5-90 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Grupo Cultural Zero 5-10-91 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Room Changes and Computer Resources 4/15/91 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - El Dia de los Muertos 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - 5 de Mayo Poster May 1991 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - 5 de Mayo 1991 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Publicity List 1991 (Bechtel Int. Center) (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Posada 12/1/90 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Adiana Martinez 4/30/91 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Annual Galarza Prize 1991 SCCR (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Program Board 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Ernesto Cardenal 11/9/90 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - La Raza Staff Assoc Fall 1990 Fiesta 11/10/90 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Alejandro Morales 11-5-90 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - MASS La Virgen Guadalupe 12/9/90 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - El Centro Chicano Staff Meetings 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Tardeada 2/1/91 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Noticias 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Newsletter 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Deans Reception 1990 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Publicity 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Teatro de la Esperanza 5/19/90 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Floricanto (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Gran Posada 1989 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - El Dia de Los Muertos 1989 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - University Lecture Fund 1989 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Chicano Students Mail list 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - CASAS Files, 1988-1990
    - Amnesty Expenditure Statements, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Literacy Project (IMBC 401), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Certificates (Stanford Literacy Project), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - No Numbers (SLP) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from IRCA/SLIAG (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - CASAS Correspondence from the Justice Dept., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Amnesty Intake (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Intake Forms: Daniel Ramirez (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Guidelines (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Client Data Sheet (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Ins Quest (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Administration (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Palo Alto Civics (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Stanford Roster (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Roster: San Juan Ellenberger (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Daniel Ramirez () (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Rosters: B. Ward (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Roster: San Jose (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Roster: Hodart (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Intake Forms (Peter Tinkelenberg) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Spanish Program (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Leon, Oscar (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - EPA 6:30 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Students' Class notes/Coursework (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Concilio de Asuntos Chicanos (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Assistant Dean Search Process (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Chicano Orientation (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Chicano Peer Counseling Class, Fall (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Chicano Community Conference (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Costano Elementary '89, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - TV Social Mixer, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Publicity (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Seminar/Reception: Latinos and the Media, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Cinco de Mayo Poster, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Rafael Zamarripa (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - CGSA Spring Forum On UCMI (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - El Teatro de la Esperanza (Cinco de Mayo 1989) (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Cinco de Mayo Reception, 1990-91 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Cinco de Mayo Salsa Party (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Luis Fragra, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Centro Programs, 1989-1990
    - Magazine Ole, 1989-90 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Centro Newsletter, 1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Burciaga Booksigning, 1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - El Centro Community Retreat (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Affirmative Action Award, 1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Centro Programs, 1987-1988
    - Lauro Cavazos, 1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Art Exhibit, Autumn 1987 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Chicano Program Coordinating Committee (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Chicano Graduation 1988 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Coffee House Event, Spring, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Chavez/Torres Debate, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Hijos: Once A Family, 1987-88 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Cinco De Mayo, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Independence HS Visitation, 1987-88 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Mexican Garment Wokers' Tour, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Mario Obledo Seminar, 1990-91 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Spring Quarter Programming (1988) (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Tressidder Art Exhibit, Spring Quarter, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Salsa, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Pro_Mo Weekend, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Pachanga, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Centro Programs, 1986-1987
    - Second Annual Awards Ceremony, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Salt of the Earth (1), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Salt of the Earth (2), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Press and Publishings, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Copier Information (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Jose Morgado-Exposicion de Poesia, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter Publications, 1986-87 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Gabino Palomares, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - "Salvador" (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Cinco de Mayo, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Centro Programs, 1985-1986
    - El Centro Newsletter, 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - La Onda, '84-'85 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Chilaquiles (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Voz de la Gente (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - CSAC Festival, 1986-87 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Immigration Conference, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Maria Benitez Reception (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Chicano Faculty Reception (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - MEChA, '85-'86, 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Cinco de Mayo Art Exhibit, 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - CSAC, 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Latino (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Mexican Earthquake Relief, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - PROCOMEXCHI Visitation, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - The Stanford Daily (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Centro Programs, 1984-1985
    - Cinco de Mayo, '84 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - "Ojos de Dios"/Zendejas (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Exploracion de Arte, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - "Chicanos in California"- Organization, Politics and people, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Graduate Student Orientation, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Chicano Graduation, '85, 1984-85 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Centro Programs, Pre 1984
    - Parties!! (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Norman Bent/"The Miskito Indians", 1985 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Dia De Los Muertos (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Posada, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Cinco De Mayo, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Arturo Islas: Reception (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Symposium on the Chicano Student Movement of '60s-'70s (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Secondary Orientation, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Graduate Spouse Orientation, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Casa Zapata: Theme House Conflicts, 1981-82 Graduate Orientation File (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Media Resources
    - Starting a Student Publication @ Stanford, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Art Exhibit, Autumn 1987 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Centro Chicano Newsletter, '81-'82 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Chicano Orientation, 1982-83 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Stanford Daily, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Chicano & Latino Organizations, 1991-1992
    - EPPASSA, 33270 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Financial Aid Office Info Mtgs., 33295 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Chicano Fellows Program, Fellowships, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Barrio Assistance Development, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Chicano/Latino Student Groups- Officers List, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Student Groups: Mexican/Chicano-Latino, 1990-91 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Ballet Folklorico, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - New Students & Info for Organizations, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - CHE, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - CGSA, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Derechos 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Estos Tiempos, 1990-91 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Estos Tiempos, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - FOCUS Group- CasaZapata, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Hispanic Business Students' Association, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Latino Business Students Association, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Latino Student Association, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Latino Leadership Opportunity Program, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Expresion, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - MEChA, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - ProFro Weekend, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Puerto Rican Graduate Student Association, 33359 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - SSCLES, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - SSCLES, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - SALSA, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Stanford Raza Medical Students Association, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Teatro Xicano, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Chicano Fellows Program, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Chicano & Latino Youth Leadership Project, 33359 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Stanford Literacy Improvement Project, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - SCCR, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Disability Resource Center, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Stanford Si Se Puede Project, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Webb Ranch Support Group, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Women's Center (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Memorial Church, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - You Can Make A Difference Conference, 33645 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Chicano/Latino Events, 1989-1991
    - Stanford Sociedad De Padres, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Possible Speakers (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Barrio Assistance, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - BA- Winter, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - CGSA Mailing List, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - CGSA Mailing List & Puerto Rican, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - CGSA, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - CHE, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Derechos, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Expresion, 33396 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Hispanic Business Student Association, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Chicano Graduacion, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Chicano Graduation Budget, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Latino Business Student Association, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - MEChA, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Fall '90 Literacy Project, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Stanford Literacy Improvement Project, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Irene Corosco - Study of Stanford Literary Project, 33025 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Stanford Society of Chicano/Latino Engineers & Scientists, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Disability Resource Center, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Center for Chicano Research, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Chicano Graduation, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Literacy Related Material, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Latino Student Association, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Literacy Project "Head Start Funding Info", 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Project Motivation, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Pro Mo Weekend, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Pro Mo, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - SLIP, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - SLIP Tutors Manual (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Tresidder Eng Class, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Stanford Literacy Improvement Project Tutors, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - CA Literacy Campaign "Judith Wilczak", 1983 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - LGBCC Community Center, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Office of Student Activities, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Public Service Network, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Centro Program Board
    - Program Proposals Winter, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Program Board Proposal Processed (or Rejected), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Spring Program Board Proposals, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - El Centro Program Board Guidelines, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Criteria & Guidelines, 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Program Board Autumn '88, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Program Board Winter '89, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Program Board Spring '89, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Program Board Autumn '87, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Program Board Winter '88, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Program Board Spring '88, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Fall 1986 Programming, 1981-82 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Program Board Autumn, '85, 1985-86 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Program Board Winter, '86, 1985-86 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Program Board Spring '86 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Program Board Spring '87, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Centro Program Board, 1984-85 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Proposals - Autumn Quarter, '84, 1984-85 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Program Board Winter '85, Proposals, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Program Board Spring '85- Proposals, 198 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1989-1990
    - VSO's, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Chicano Student Organizations, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Chicano/Latino Graduacion, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - CGSA, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - 1989-90 Chicano Sourcebook, 1991-92 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1988-1989
    - CLOC, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Derechos (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - MEChA, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - MEChA Special Fee, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Project Motivation, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Chicano Student Organization, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Spring ASSU Ballot, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Ballet Folklorico, 1989-90 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Barrio Assistance, 1987-88 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Hispanic Business Students' Association, 1991-92 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - National Hispanic Democrats, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Minority Leaders of the Future, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Project Motivation, 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - SALUd- Stanford Alliance of Latino Undergrads, 1991-92 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - SSCLES, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Public Service Center, 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - CHE, 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Buddy Program, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - La Chicana Colectiva, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - CGSA, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - CORE, 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - MEChA, 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Minority Outreach (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Chicano/Latino Events, 1989-1991
    - Museums & Exhibitions, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Chuy Negrete, 1978-88 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Jesus Negrete, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Juan Pina, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - El Publico, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - The Puerto Rican Diaspora, 1987-88 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Miguel Angel Quijada, 1987-88 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Eureka Theatre Company, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - La Compania de teatro de Albuquerque, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Sabia (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Teatro Nacional de Aztlan (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Teatro Campesino/Luis Valdez, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Xochipilli (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - People
    - Profiles, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Thomas Ambrogi, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Gloria Ansolua (Writer/Poet), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Jose Antonio Burciaga, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Max Camarillo, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Karla King, 1987-88 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Richard Rodriguez, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Personnel, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Foundations
    - Columbia Foundation, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Coro Foundation, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Eyes of the World Foundation, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)